export const mockqna = [
  {
    question: "jock lit hip goo keys",
    answer: "chocolate chip cookies"
  },
  {
    question: "high dance eek",
    answer: "hide and seek"
  },
  {
    question: "reef idge her ate her",
    answer: "refrigerator"
  },
  {
    question: "is bunch pops queer pans",
    answer: "spongebob squarepants"
  },
  {
    question: "shack cough alt raids",
    answer: "jack of all trades"
  },
  {
    question: "Boe day tote ships",
    answer: "potato chips"
  },
  {
    question: "ha minch ease",
    answer: "ham and cheese"
  },
  {
    question: "she is burg her",
    answer: "cheeseburger"
  },
  {
    question: "highs creek own",
    answer: "ice cream cone"
  },
  {
    question: "jock lit prow knees",
    answer: "chocolate brownies"
  },
  {
    question: "hap pulled use",
    answer: "apple juice"
  },
  {
    question: "jik hin ugh its",
    answer: "chicken nuggets"
  },
  {
    question: "fur rose in yoke hurt",
    answer: "frozen yogurt"
  },
  {
    question: "ewe night ted king dumb",
    answer: "united kingdom"
  },
  {
    question: "veer off mess sing oat",
    answer: "fear of missing out"
  },
]

export default mockqna